Guide to the Records of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center RG.42.5
New York University Archives
- Series I: Exhibition Files, 1961-2004
  - Life -- Information and Publicity, 1978 March-1979 June; cuid2418 (Box I:17, Folder 30)
  - LIfe -- Manual, Circa 1979-1981; cuid2419 (Box I:17, Folder 31)
  - Life -- Miscellaneous, 1972-1979; cuid2420 (Box I:17, Folder 32)
  - Life -- Photograph Titles, 1979 May; cuid2421 (Box I:17, Folder 33)
  - Life -- Village Night, 1979 May-June; cuid2422 (Box I:17, Folder 34)
  - American Painting -- Artist File, 1979 June-1981 April; cuid2423 (Box I:18, Folder 1)
  - American Painting -- Fact Sheets, 1979; cuid2424 (Box I:18, Folder 2)
  - American Painting -- General, 1979 April-September; cuid2425 (Box I:18, Folder 3)
  - American Painting -- Miscellaneous, 1979 March-September; cuid2426 (Box I:18, Folder 4)
  - American Painting -- Opening September 11, 1979 May-October; cuid2427 (Box I:18, Folder 5)
  - American Painting -- Symposium (1 of 3), 1979 October; cuid2428 (Box I:18, Folder 6)
  - American Painting -- Symposium (2 of 3), 1979 October; cuid2429 (Box I:18, Folder 7)
  - American Painting -- Symposium (3 of 3), 1979 October; cuid2430 (Box I:18, Folder 8)
  - American Painting -- Traveling Reviews, etc., 1979 July-December; cuid2431 (Box I:18, Folder 9)
  - American Symbolist -- October 23 Opening, 1979 October; cuid2432 (Box I:18, Folder 10)
  - American Symbolist -- Corespondence, Circa 1976-1981; cuid2433 (Box I:18, Folder 11)
  - American Symbolist -- Correspondence (Photos), 1977 December-1980 February; cuid2434 (Box I:18, Folder 12)
  - American Symbolist -- Correspondence (Spencer Museum), 1977 January-1980 June; cuid2435 (Box I:18, Folder 13)
  - American Symbolist -- Fact Sheets, 1979; cuid2436 (Box I:18, Folder 14)
  - American Symbolist -- Miscellaneous, 1979 February-November; cuid2437 (Box I:18, Folder 15)
  - American Symbolist -- Pivar Notes, Circa 1977-1980; cuid2438 (Box I:18, Folder 16)
  - American Symbolist -- Press Releases, 1979 October-November; cuid2439 (Box I:18, Folder 17)
  - American Symbolist -- Research (1 of 2), 1978-1979; cuid2440 (Box I:18, Folder 18)
  - American Symbolist -- Research (2 of 2), 1972-1979; cuid2441 (Box I:18, Folder 19)
  - Charles Gleyre -- Acknowledgements, Circa 1978-1980; cuid2442 (Box I:18, Folder 20)
  - Charles Gleyre -- Correspondence (Hauptman-Scott), 1978 August-1980 July; cuid2443 (Box I:18, Folder 21)
  - Charles Gleyre -- Correspondence (Luthy-ProHelvetia), 1976 August-1981 July; cuid2444 (Box I:18, Folder 22)
  - Charles Gleyre -- Musee Cantonal Labels, Circa 1978-1981; cuid2445 (Box I:18, Folder 23)
  - Charles Gleyre -- Press Releases, 1980; cuid2446 (Box I:18, Folder 24)
  - Charles Gleyre -- Fact Sheets, 1980; cuid2447 (Box I:18, Folder 25)
  - Charles Gleyre -- Miscellaneous, 1977-1982 June; cuid2448 (Box I:18, Folder 26)
  - Charles Gleyre -- Robert R. Littman Miscellaneous File, 1977 August-1981 February; cuid2449 (Box I:18, Folder 27)
  - David Hockney -- Background, Clippings and Other Miscellaneous, 1977 May-1980 March; cuid2450 (Box I:18, Folder 28)
  - David Hockney -- Billboard, 1980 February-June; cuid2451 (Box I:18, Folder 29)
  - David Hockney -- Evening on Wheels Press Release, 1980; cuid2452 (Box I:18, Folder 30)
  - David Hockney -- Miscellaneous Information on Artist (1 of 2), 1978 March-1980 September; cuid2453 (Box I:18, Folder 31)
  - David Hockney -- Miscellaneous Information on Artist (2 of 2), 1978-1980; cuid2454 (Box I:18, Folder 32)
  - David Hockney -- Parade/Metropolitan Opera, 1981 February-March; cuid2455 (Box I:18, Folder 33)
  - David Hockney -- Press/Literature, 1978-1982 August; cuid2456 (Box I:18, Folder 34)
  - David Hockney -- Sale Items, 1970-1977; cuid2457 (Box I:18, Folder 35)
  - American Stereographs -- Correspondence and Other Miscellaneous, 1980 May-September; cuid2458 (Box I:18, Folder 36)
  - American Stereographs -- Fact Sheets, 1980; cuid2459 (Box I:18, Folder 37)
  - American Stereographs -- Press Releases, 1980; cuid2460 (Box I:18, Folder 38)
  - American Stereographs -- Publicity and Other Miscellaneous, 1979 April-1980 April; cuid2461 (Box I:18, Folder 39)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Audio Guide, Circa 1979-1980; cuid2462 (Box I:18, Folder 40)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Duration: 25 minutes
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Audio Guide (Braille), Circa 1979-1980; cuid2463 (Box I:18, Folder 41)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Audio Guide (Miscellaneous Research), Circa 1978-1980; cuid2464 (Box I:18, Folder 42)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Biographies, Circa 1978-1980; cuid2465 (Box I:18, Folder 43)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Background Material (1 of 2), 1977-1978; cuid2466 (Box I:19, Folder 1)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Background Material (2 of 2), 1977-1982; cuid2467 (Box I:19, Folder 2)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Deaf, 1982 April; cuid2468 (Box I:19, Folder 3)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Fact Sheets, 1980; cuid2469 (Box I:19, Folder 4)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Press Releases, 1980; cuid2470 (Box I:19, Folder 5)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Publicity Mailing Lists, Circa 1978-1980; cuid2471 (Box I:19, Folder 6)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Reference on Handicapped, 1973 December-1981 May; cuid2472 (Box I:19, Folder 7)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Research (1 of 2), 1976 August-1978 November; cuid2473 (Box I:19, Folder 8)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Research (2 of 2), 1975-1978; cuid2474 (Box I:19, Folder 9)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Responses to Susan Cuddeback (Research), 1976 March-1979 April; cuid2475 (Box I:19, Folder 10)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Robert Littman's File, 1976-1980; cuid2476 (Box I:19, Folder 11)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Sources of Information, Circa 1978-1980; cuid2477 (Box I:19, Folder 12)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Susan Cuddeback Summary, 1979-1980; cuid2478 (Box I:19, Folder 13)
  - Sheldon Levison (Sept. 3-7, 1980), 1965-1980; cuid2479 (Box I:19, Folder 14)
  - Sheldon Levison -- Press Releases, 1980 August; cuid2480 (Box I:19, Folder 15)
  - Grey Fall Schedule Press Release, 1980; cuid2481 (Box I:19, Folder 16)
  - Walter Gay -- Catalog, 1980 August-1982 February; cuid2482 (Box I:19, Folder 17)
  - Walter Gay -- Press Literature, 1979 April-1981 January; cuid2483 (Box I:19, Folder 18)
  - Walter Gay -- Research, 1978 February-1980 November; cuid2484 (Box I:19, Folder 19)
  - Walter Gay -- Research Trip to Paris, 1979 October-December; cuid2485 (Box I:19, Folder 20)
  - Sonia Delaunay -- Background and Drafts, 1980; cuid2486 (Box I:19, Folder 21)
  - Sonia Delaunay -- Boutique, 1977-1980; cuid2487 (Box I:19, Folder 22)
  - Sonia Delaunay -- Lecture Series, 1980-1981; cuid2488 (Box I:19, Folder 23)
  - Sonia Delaunay -- Press Literature, 1979 December-1981 February; cuid2489 (Box I:19, Folder 24)
  - Sonia Delaunay -- Robert Littman's File (Lists and Other Miscellaneous), Circa 1980; cuid2490 (Box I:19, Folder 25)
  - Advance Exhibit Schedule (Winter-Spring 1981), 1980; cuid2491 (Box I:19, Folder 26)
  - Court of Benin -- Miscellaneous, 1979-1981; cuid2492 (Box I:19, Folder 27)
  - Court of Benin -- Press/Literature, 1980 April-1981January; cuid2493 (Box I:19, Folder 28)
  - Italian Dwarings -- Long Island Tour, 1980-1981; cuid2494 (Box I:19, Folder 29)
  - Italian Drawings -- Press, 1980-1981; cuid2495 (Box I:19, Folder 30)
  - Tracking the Marvelous -- Catalog, Circa 1980-1981; cuid2496 (Box I:19, Folder 31)
  - Tracking the Marvelous -- Catalog (John Myers Essay), Circa 1980-1981; cuid2497 (Box I:19, Folder 32)
  - Tracking the Marvelous -- Correspondence, 1980 October-1981 July; cuid2498 (Box I:19, Folder 33)
  - Tracking the Marvelous -- John Myers Press/Literature, 1979 November-1981 July; cuid2499 (Box I:19, Folder 34)
  - Tracking the Marvelous -- Press Release, 1981; cuid2500 (Box I:19, Folder 35)
  - Space Photography -- Book (1 of 2), 1978-1981; cuid2501 (Box I:19, Folder 36)
  - Space Photography -- Book (2 of 2), 1982; cuid2502 (Box I:19, Folder 37)
  - Space Photography -- Catalogue, 1980-1981; cuid2503 (Box I:19, Folder 38)
  - Space Photography -- Catalogue and Other Miscellaneous, 1981; cuid2504 (Box I:19, Folder 39)
  - Photography of Space -- French Research, Circa 1980-1981; cuid2505 (Box I:19, Folder 40)
  - Space Photography -- Image Requests (JPL), 1981 January-June; cuid2506 (Box I:19, Folder 41)
  - Space Photography -- Motorola, 1979-1982 May; cuid2507 (Box I:19, Folder 42)
  - Photography of Space -- Note Cards, 1981; cuid2508 (Box I:19, Folder 43)
  - Space Photography -- Photo Captions, 1981; cuid2509 (Box I:19, Folder 44)
  - Space Photography -- Photos, 1981 January-April; cuid2510 (Box I:19, Folder 45)
  - Space Photography -- Press/Literature (1 of 3), 1976-1981; cuid2511 (Box I:19, Folder 46)
  - Space Photography -- Press/Literature (2 of 3), 1979 August-1981 August; cuid2512 (Box I:20, Folder 1)
  - Space Photography -- Press/Literature (3 of 3), 1979 December-1983 January; cuid2513 (Box I:20, Folder 2)
  - Space Photography -- Press Release, 1981 June-December; cuid2514 (Box I:20, Folder 3)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Advance and Press Release, 1981; cuid2515 (Box I:20, Folder 4)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Andre Kertesz (Photo Copies), Circa 1980-1981; cuid2516 (Box I:20, Folder 5)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Andre Kertesz (Gallatin Ass.), 1980-1983; cuid2517 (Box I:20, Folder 6)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Brademas Collection, 1981; cuid2518 (Box I:20, Folder 7)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Miscellaneous, 1976-1981; cuid2519 (Box I:20, Folder 8)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Planning and General Memos, 1980-1981; cuid2520 (Box I:20, Folder 9)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Ralph Fasanella, 1980-1981; cuid2521 (Box I:20, Folder 10)
  - Tanya Grosman (Small Gallery), 1981 April-1982 August; cuid2522 (Box I:20, Folder 11)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Book Draft 2, Circa 1979-1982; cuid2523 (Box I:20, Folder 12)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Brochure, 1981; cuid2524 (Box I:20, Folder 13)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Catalog, 1981; cuid2525 (Box I:20, Folder 14)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Description of Exhibition, Circa 1979-1981; cuid2526 (Box I:20, Folder 15)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Installation Layout, CIrca 1980-1981; cuid2527 (Box I:20, Folder 16)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Pollock Beauborg Trip (Pompideau, France), 1981-1982; cuid2528 (Box I:20, Folder 17)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Press/Literature (1 of 2), 1979-1982; cuid2529 (Box I:20, Folder 18)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Press/Literature (2 of 2), 1979-1982; cuid2530 (Box I:20, Folder 19)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Works in Exhibition and Values, 1980 February-1981 June; cuid2531 (Box I:20, Folder 20)
  - Ridiculous Theater, 1981; cuid2532 (Box I:20, Folder 21)
  - Chris Wilmarth (Exhibition Not Held), 1980 December-1981 December; cuid2533 (Box I:20, Folder 22)
  - Judson Dance Theater -- Bennington College, Circa 1980-1982; cuid2534 (Box I:20, Folder 23)
  - Judson Dance Theater -- Final NYSCA Presentation (Visual Material), 1981-1982; cuid2535 (Box I:20, Folder 24)
  - Judson Dance Theater -- Press Releases, Circa 1981-1982; cuid2536 (Box I:20, Folder 25)
  - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Press Literature, 1978-1982; cuid2537 (Box I:20, Folder 26)
  - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Catalog (1 of 2), 1981-1982; cuid2538 (Box I:20, Folder 27)
  - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Catalog (2 of 2), 1978-1982; cuid2539 (Box I:20, Folder 28)
  - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Press Releases, Circa 1981-1982; cuid2540 (Box I:20, Folder 29)
  - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Audio Cassette (Ker-Seymer, Billy Chappell), 1980 July; cuid2541 (Box I:20, Folder 30)
  - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Check List for Photographs, Circa 1981-1982; cuid2542 (Box I:20, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous Grey Press and Printed Material, 1985-1988; cuid2543 (Box I:20, Folder 32)
  - Stewart Wilson, 1981; cuid2544 (Box I:3, Folder 23)
  - Edward Henderson, 1981-1982; cuid2545 (Box I:3, Folder 24)
  - Around the Square (1 of 2), 1979-1980; cuid2546 (Box I:3, Folder 25)
  - Around the Square (2 of 2), 1979-1980; cuid2547 (Box I:3, Folder 26)
  - Around the Square -- Old Photographs and Curatorial Notes, circa 1980-1982; cuid2548 (Box I:3, Folder 27)
  - Around the Square -- Press/Literature (1 of 3), 1980-1982; cuid2549 (Box I:3, Folder 28)
  - Around the Square -- Press/Literature (2 of 3), 1980-1982; cuid2550 (Box I:3, Folder 29)
  - Around the Square -- Press/Literature (3 of 3), 1980-1982; cuid2551 (Box I:3, Folder 30)
  - Around the Square -- Correspondence, 1980 June-1982 June; cuid2552 (Box I:3, Folder 31)
  - Around the Square -- Window Installations (1 of 2), 1981-1982; cuid2553 (Box I:3, Folder 32)
  - Around the Square -- Window Installations (2 of 2), 1981-1982; cuid2554 (Box I:3, Folder 33)
  - Around the Square -- Mindy Cantor, 1981 April-1982 October; cuid2555 (Box I:3, Folder 34)
  - Around the Square -- Applebaum, 1981 December 3-1982 January 12; cuid2556 (Box I:3, Folder 35)
  - Around the Square -- Walking Tours, 1982; cuid2557 (Box I:3, Folder 36)
  - Around the Square -- PR Information, 1982; cuid2558 (Box I:3, Folder 37)
  - Bill Komosky, 1982 March-August; cuid2559 (Box I:3, Folder 38)
  - Audubon -- Exhibition Research (Inquiries to Owners), 1981-1982; cuid2560 (Box I:3, Folder 39)
  - Audubon -- General Correspondence, 1982; cuid2561 (Box I:3, Folder 40)
  - John James Audubon and His Sons - Final NYSCA Presentation, 1982 March-May; cuid2562 (Box I:3, Folder 41)
  - Audubon -- Magazine, 1982 January-February; cuid2563 (Box I:3, Folder 42)
  - Audubon -- PR, 1982 January-1983 June; cuid2564 (Box I:3, Folder 43)
  - Hare/Kiesler -- Press Photos, 1982; cuid2565 (Box I:3, Folder 44)
  - Hare/Kiesler -- Two Installations, 1982 April-June; cuid2566 (Box I:3, Folder 45)
  - Hare/Kiesler -- Publicity/Biographical Information, 1979 February-1983 January; cuid2567 (Box I:3, Folder 46)
  - Morse -- Packets of Reviews, 1982 July-1983 October; cuid2568 (Box I:3, Folder 47)
  - Morse -- Promotion, 1982 July-1983 January; cuid2569 (Box I:3, Folder 48)
  - Morse -- Photographs, 1982 June 17-1984 September 7; cuid2570 (Box I:3, Folder 49)
  - Morse -- Paul J. Strati, undated; cuid2571 (Box I:3, Folder 50)
  - Morse -- Lectures and Gallery Talks, 1982 September-1983 March; cuid2572 (Box I:3, Folder 51)
  - Morse -- Negatives of Text Labels, 1982-1983; cuid2573 (Box I:3, Folder 52)
  - Morse -- Works Not in Exhibition, 1982 August-1983 January; cuid2574 (Box I:3, Folder 53)
  - Morse -- Paul Stati, 1980 November-1983 December; cuid2575 (Box I:3, Folder 54)
  - Morse -- Benefit Preview, 1982 September; cuid2576 (Box I:3, Folder 55)
  - Morse -- Benefit Opening and Viewing, 1982 August-September; cuid2577 (Box I:3, Folder 56)
  - Morse -- Research, 1834-1872; cuid2578 (Box I:3, Folder 57)
  - Morse -- Correspondence, 1980 July-1984 March; cuid2579 (Box I:3, Folder 58)
  - Faces -- Bob's File, 1982-1983; cuid2580 (Box I:4, Folder 1)
  - Portrait Photography PR, 1982 August-November; cuid2581 (Box I:4, Folder 2)
  - Face to Face, 1981 February-1983 January; cuid2582 (Box I:4, Folder 3)
  - Faces Photographed, 1982 October-November; cuid2583 (Box I:4, Folder 4)
  - Frida Kahlo Information, undated; cuid2584 (Box I:4, Folder 5)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- Publicity Photographs, undated; cuid2585 (Box I:4, Folder 6)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- Whitechapel Correspondence, 1981 October-1983 March; cuid2586 (Box I:4, Folder 7)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- at Whitechapel Art Gallery, 1982; cuid2587 (Box I:4, Folder 8)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- Labels, circa 1982-1983; cuid2588 (Box I:4, Folder 9)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- Catalog and Reproductions (1 of 2), 1982-1983; cuid2589 (Box I:4, Folder 10)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- Catalog and Reproductions (2 of 2), 1982-1983; cuid2590 (Box I:4, Folder 11)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- General Correspondence, 1982 January-1983 September; cuid2591 (Box I:4, Folder 12)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- PR (1 of 2), 1982 March-1983 October; cuid2592 (Box I:4, Folder 13)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- PR (2 of 2), 1982 March-1983 October; cuid2593 (Box I:4, Folder 14)
  - Bob's File -- Kahlo/Modotti, 1982 July-1983 January; cuid2594 (Box I:4, Folder 15)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- Press Release and Exhibition Description, 1983; cuid2595 (Box I:4, Folder 16)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- Review Packets, 1983 March-April; cuid2596 (Box I:4, Folder 17)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- Photographs, 1985 June-July; cuid2597 (Box I:4, Folder 18)
  - Bergdorf/Montana Committee and Publicity, 1983; cuid2598 (Box I:4, Folder 19)
  - Bob's Bergdorf/Montana, 1982-1983; cuid2599 (Box I:4, Folder 20)
  - Turkish Exhibition -- AXIA, 1977-1983; cuid2600 (Box I:4, Folder 21)
  - Turkish Exhibition, 1979 March-1983 August; cuid2601 (Box I:4, Folder 22)
  - Ottoman Show -- Label Copy, circa 1982-1983; cuid2602 (Box I:4, Folder 23)
  - Turkish Exhibition -- Items (1 of 2), circa 1982-1983; cuid2603 (Box I:4, Folder 24)
  - Turkish Exhibition -- Items (2 of 2), circa 1982-1983; cuid2604 (Box I:4, Folder 25)
  - Bob's File - TAT (Turkish Exhibit), 1982 July-1983 August; cuid2605 (Box I:4, Folder 26)
  - Turkish Exhibition -- Object List from AIXA, 1982 December; cuid2606 (Box I:4, Folder 27)
  - Ottoman Show and Reception PR and Invitation, 1982 December-1983 June; cuid2607 (Box I:4, Folder 28)
  - Petropoulos Papers [Turkish Exhibition], 1983 April-1984 January; cuid2608 (Box I:4, Folder 29)
  - Abby Weed Grey Exhibit -- Press Photos, circa 1983; cuid2609 (Box I:4, Folder 30)
  - Paul Outerbridge -- Description, undated; cuid2610 (Box I:4, Folder 31)
  - Paul Outerbridge -- Correspondence, 1981 July-1984 March; cuid2611 (Box I:4, Folder 32)
  - Paul Outerbridge -- Press, 1982 February-1983 October; cuid2612 (Box I:4, Folder 33)
  - Eva Hesse -- Press and PR (1983), 1979-1983; cuid2613 (Box I:4, Folder 34)
  - Eva Hesse, 1983; cuid2614 (Box I:4, Folder 35)
  - Louise Dahl -- Wolfe Press, 1953-1983 December; cuid2615 (Box I:4, Folder 36)
  - Louise Dahl -- Wolfe Installation, 1983; cuid2616 (Box I:4, Folder 37)
  - Louise Dahl -- Wolfe RRL File, 1983; cuid2617 (Box I:4, Folder 38)
  - Dahl-Wolfe -- Interview, 1982 December 9; cuid2618 (Box I:4, Folder 39)
  - Louise Dahl-Wolfe -- Interview (Cassette), 1982 December 9; cuid2619 (Box I:4, Folder 40)
  - Louise Dahl-Wolfe -- Correspondence, 1982 May - 1983 September; cuid2620 (Box I:4, Folder 41)
  - Louise Dahl-Wolfe -- Dinner, 1983 August - September; cuid2621 (Box I:4, Folder 42)
  - Louise Dahl-Wolfe -- Magazine, 1981 June; cuid2622 (Box I:4, Folder 43)
  - Louise Dahl-Wolfe -- Staley-Wise Press Release, circa 1983; cuid2623 (Box I:4, Folder 44)
  - Permament Art Collection Exhibit, 1983; cuid2624 (Box I:4, Folder 45)
  - Permanent Art Collection Exhibit -- Labels, 1983; cuid2625 (Box I:4, Folder 46)
  - Ken Tisa, 1983 November; cuid2626 (Box I:4, Folder 47)
  - Picasso -- Hockney Essay, undated; cuid2627 (Box I:4, Folder 48)
  - Picasso -- Schiff Essay, Undated; cuid2628 (Box I:5, Folder 1)
  - Picasso -- Schiff, 1984 May-June; cuid2629 (Box I:5, Folder 2)
  - Picasso -- Catalogue, 1983; cuid2630 (Box I:5, Folder 3)
  - Picasso -- Publications, 1983-1984; cuid2631 (Box I:5, Folder 4)
  - Picasso -- Press, 1983 June-November; cuid2632 (Box I:5, Folder 5)
  - Picasso -- Proposal (Various Drafts), circa 1982-1983; cuid2633 (Box I:5, Folder 6)
  - Picasso -- Acknowledgements, circa 1982-1984; cuid2634 (Box I:5, Folder 7)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Krannert Art Museum, 1961; cuid2635 (Box I:5, Folder 8)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Exhibition, 1983 September-1984 June; cuid2636 (Box I:5, Folder 9)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Installation, circa 1984; cuid2637 (Box I:5, Folder 10)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Bob's File, 1983 December-1984 March; cuid2638 (Box I:5, Folder 11)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Correspondence to Newport Harbor, 1984 February-May; cuid2639 (Box I:5, Folder 12)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Northern California Figs. (Press; 1 of 2), 1979 June-1981 July; cuid2640 (Box I:5, Folder 13)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Northern California Figs. (Press; 2 of 2), 1979 October-1984 July; cuid2641 (Box I:5, Folder 14)
  - Bay Area Painting -- North California Figs. (Correspondence), 1980 February-1984 January; cuid2642 (Box I:5, Folder 15)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Joan Brown (Hansen Fuller Goldeen Gallery), 1978-1982 May; cuid2643 (Box I:5, Folder 16)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Catalogue, 1984 January-March; cuid2644 (Box I:5, Folder 17)
  - Bay Area Painting/Northern California Figs. -- Nathan Oliveira, 1980; cuid2645 (Box I:5, Folder 18)
  - Bay Area Painting/North California -- Action/Precision Catalogue, 1983-1984 January 25; cuid2646 (Box I:5, Folder 19)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Checklist, 1984 February-May; cuid2647 (Box I:5, Folder 20)
  - Jean Cocteau -- Paris, May 1983, After 1915; cuid2648 (Box I:5, Folder 21)
  - Jean Cocteau -- Paris, May 1983(Littman and McCready), 1983 March-May; cuid2649 (Box I:5, Folder 22)
  - Cocteau -- Invitation(Hill and Knowlton), Circa 1981-1984; cuid2650 (Box I:5, Folder 23)
  - Jean Cocteau -- Correspondence (1 of 3), 1983 August-December; cuid2651 (Box I:5, Folder 24)
  - Jean Cocteau -- Correspondence (2 of 3), 1982 October-1983 August; cuid2652 (Box I:5, Folder 25)
  - Jean Cocteau -- Correspondence (3 of 3), 1980 June-1982 November; cuid2653 (Box I:5, Folder 26)
  - Jean Cocteau -- Parade Curtain, 1983 October-November; cuid2654 (Box I:5, Folder 27)
  - Jean Cocteau -- Press, 1980 June-1984 November; cuid2655 (Box I:5, Folder 28)
  - Cocteau -- Literature, 1984 February-November; cuid2656 (Box I:5, Folder 29)
  - Jean Cocteau-- RRL File, 1981-1983; cuid2657 (Box I:5, Folder 30)
  - Jean Cocteau -- Summary, 1984 March-November; cuid2658 (Box I:5, Folder 31)
  - Cocteau -- Catalogue, Circa 1983-1984; cuid2659 (Box I:5, Folder 32)
  - L'Atelier Mourlot -- Press Material (1 of 2), 1948 November-1984 July; cuid2660 (Box I:5, Folder 33)
  - L'Atelier Mourlot -- Press Material (2 of 2), 1965; cuid2661 (Box I:5, Folder 34)
  - L'Atelier Mourlot -- Installation and Gallery Reception, 1984 July; cuid2662 (Box I:5, Folder 35)
  - L'Atelier Mourlot -- Invitation, 1984 June-August; cuid2663 (Box I:5, Folder 36)
  - Boldini -- Photographs (Poster), 1984; cuid2664 (Box I:5, Folder 37)
  - Boldini -- Photographs, 1984; cuid2665 (Box I:5, Folder 38)
  - Boldini -- Catalogue, 1984 November; cuid2666 (Box I:5, Folder 39)
  - Boldini -- Catalogue, 1984; cuid2667 (Box I:5, Folder 40)
  - Boldini Giovanni (November 13-December 22, 1984), 1984 October-1985 April; cuid2668 (Box I:5, Folder 41)
  - Action/Precision -- Al Held, 1982; cuid2669 (Box I:5, Folder 42)
  - Action/Precision -- Reviews, 1984 June-1985 January; cuid2670 (Box I:5, Folder 43)
  - Action/Precision -- Invitation, 1984 December-1985 January; cuid2671 (Box I:5, Folder 44)
  - Action/Precision -- Press Photos, 1984 December-1985 January; cuid2672 (Box I:5, Folder 45)
  - Action/Precision -- Information and Press, 1984 December-1985 January; cuid2673 (Box I:5, Folder 46)
  - Action/Precision -- Press Release, 1984 June-December; cuid2674 (Box I:5, Folder 47)
  - Action/Precision -- Symposium Tape, 1985 January-1986 September; cuid2675 (Box I:5, Cassette 48, E-records nyuarchives_rg42.5, E-records cuid2675)
    Format: 1/8" audiocassette, Duration: 84 min, Preservation note: Audio is low-quality and inaudible.
  - Precious -- Exhibit, 1985 February-September; cuid2676 (Box I:5, Folder 49)
  - Precious -- Correspondence, 1984 December-1985 May; cuid2677 (Box I:5, Folder 50)
  - Precious -- Images and Conditions, Circa 1985; cuid2678 (Box I:5, Folder 51)
  - Precious -- Press(1 of 2), 1985 March-September; cuid2679 (Box I:5, Folder 52)
  - Precious -- Press(2 of 2), 1986 January-June; cuid2680 (Box I:6, Folder 1)